question_data =[{"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten&#039;s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to it as the &quot;Dark Times&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An episode of &quot;The Simpsons&quot; is dedicated to Moe Szyslak&#039;s bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;The Simpsons&quot; family is named after creator Matt Groening&#039;s real family.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]